Okay, I'll start by looking for bold.
我先查找粗体元素
To do that I will hit Cmd+F and then search for bold.
使用 Cmd 和 F 键 查找粗体(bold)
Now this brings me to a bold faced element called &lt;b&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;
查找到了一个粗体元素 &lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;
That looks pretty reasonable, but
看起来不错
it may be hard to see there is a second search result.
这里可能不太容易注意到 但是还有第二个查找结果
So I'm going hit enter again. And that brings me to the strong element.
所以我再按回车键 我们可以看到 &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; 元素
Now the strong element is something that has importance and
这里写了 &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; 元素更强调内容的重要性
is typically displayed in bold.
通常以粗体显示
In fact I recommend using strong.
事实上我更推荐使用 &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; 元素
Let me show you how that looks.
下面我给大家展示一下效果
So I've gone ahead and wrapped the text with a strong tag and
我已经添加了 &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; 元素
as I said the b would be fine too if you did that.
正如我刚才所说 也可以使用 &lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt; 元素
And then I've saved it and I will come over to the browser and hit refresh and
然后我保存了修改 在浏览器刷新页面
then wallah the text is bold.
可以看到文本显示为粗体了
Okay next up.
接下来
I need to make this text emphasized.
我需要着重强调这些文本
Back inside the Mozilla developer network I'm going to search for
我回到 Mozilla Developer Network 查找
emphasis.
着重(emphasis)
There we go. And that quickly takes me to
查找结果为 &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; 元素
the em element which you saw before.
你们刚才也看到这个元素了
The element marks that something has a lot of importance and
这里写了 &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; 元素用于标记出着重阅读的内容
so that looks good to me.
看起来很合适
You'll also note that right underneath it you'll have something called i.
大家也可以看到在下面有一个 &lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt; 元素
I will make something italic incidentally.
&lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt; 会给内容加上斜体
But you actually aren't supposed to use the  element for any itallics.
但是你不应该使用 &lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt; 元素来实现斜体效果
It actually has a different purpose now which you can read about here.
这里已经写明了 它实际上是有其他的用途
Let me show you how the element looks.
下面给大家展示一下效果
So, i've added the opening tag and the closing tag.
我已经将开放标签和闭合标签
Around This content.
加在了内容的起始处和结尾处
And then I'll come over to the browser and hit refresh.
然后在浏览器点击刷新页面
And there you go.
可以看到
This text is now emphasized.
现在这些文本被着重强调了
Incidentally, in the next lesson you'll be learning another way
在下一节课中 大家也可以学习到
of making text bold and italics.
实现文本粗体和斜体效果的其他方式
I hope you remember that there are many ways to accomplish a lot of tasks
希望大家记住 在浏览器中很多任务都是可以通过多种方式
inside the browser.
实现的